wetransfer.info 2011-05-19

# 1. Who is WeTransfer.com?

                                     PRIVACY POLICY                                                           p1
WeTransfer.com takes your privacy very seriously and will process and use information about you in
a secure manner. This Privacy Policy gives a review of the measurements WeTransfer has taken to
guarantee your privacy. This Privacy Policy is written for everybody who visits the Website of WeTransfer.
com, especially the ones who use the service of WeTransfer through the Site. We therefore recommend
that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. The capitalized words in this Privacy Policy are defined in the
Terms of Use of WeTransfer.com as well as the Corporate Terms of Use of WeTransfer.com.
Please be advised that this Privacy Policy is based on Dutch law. If the legislation in the jurisdiction you
are living in prohibits or limits your use of the Service, you are responsible for abiding to this legislation.
1. Who is WeTransfer.com?
WeTransfer.com is a premium service-providing company in the area of digital file transferring. The
Service allows users to send files (up to 2 GB) to one or more recipients identified by a valid email
address.
WeTransfer is based in Amsterdam, The Netherlands at the Nieuwe Prinsengracht 33 (1018 EG) and is
listed at the Chamber of Commerce under number 34380998. WeTransfer.com also has offices in San
Francisco. United States of America, in the Flood Building at 870 Market Street, CA 94102.
2. What Personal Information is collected and processed by WeTransfer.com?
Log Data
When you visit the Site and/or use the Service, our servers automatically record information about your
use of the Service and your visit to the Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data includes the filename and file
size of all files that you transfer by means of the Service. The Log Data may also include information
such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, the sender email address and receiver(s) email
address, the browser type, what software you are using, the web page you were visiting immediately
prior to visiting our Site, pages of our Site that you visited, the time spent on those pages, information
you searched for on our Site, access times and dates, other statistics and “cookies”.
Account data
If you have downloaded the Desktop Application from the Site, you must create an Account in order to
use the Service. When you create such an Account, you are asked to fill out certain information about
yourself. You can always adjust the information you have provided.
Corporate Information
If you have entered into a Corporate Subscription with WeTransfer.com you must create an Account,
in order to use the Service. When you create such an Account, you are asked provide certain Personal
Information. You can always adjust the information you have provided.
3. What are Cookies and how is WeTransfer.com using them?
Like many websites, WeTransfer uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that
we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. WeTransfer uses cookies for two
purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future
logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better
understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by users of the Service and
general web traffic on the Site. We link the information we store in cookies to the Personal Information
you submit to us while you are on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from
your computer when you close your browser.
Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. WeTransfer does not
have access to or control of any cookies that its advertisers may store in your browser and this Privacy
Policy does not apply to the use of cookies by advertisers.
You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you
before accepting a cookie from the web sites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may
not be able to use all portions of the Site or all the functionality of the Service. In order to know more
about the possibility to stop accepting cookies we advise you to consult your browser instruction or the
“Help” function in your browser.

                                     PRIVACY POLICY                                                        p2
4. For what purpose will WeTransfer.com use your Personal Information?
Purposes
WeTransfer.com will use your Personal Information for the following purposes:
   • to provide the Service to you; and
   • t o send information to you about WeTransfer.com’s own, similar services such as updates and
      promotional actions of WeTransfer.com; and
   • to draw up statistical data, to improve the Service and to protect the Service; and
   • to provide your information to third parties pursuant to legal obligations.
Use by WeTransfer.com
In order to perform the Services that are requested by you through our Site, WeTransfer.com will
necessarily use (some) the Personal Information you provided.
In addition thereto, WeTransfer.com will keep you informed of the development of its Service. If an
expansion is on its way or an update is created, or in case of promotional actions of WeTransfer.com,
WeTransfer.com will inform you thereof by email. If you do not want to receive any messages about the
Service, you can unsubscribe via this email address [url]. In addition, each individual message includes
the possibility to unsubscribe. Please do keep a close eye on the Site so that you know when there is
a new update or expansion. Furthermore, please be advised that WeTransfer.com also sends emails in
order to correctly provide the Service to you. These emails are essential to the Service. It is therefore not
possible to unsubscribe for these emails.
WeTransfer.com uses the Log Data for statistical purposes as well as for protection of the Site and the
Service. WeTransfer.com furthermore uses this Log Data to monitor and analyze use of the Site and
the Service and for the Site’s technical administration, to improve the Site’s functionality and user-
friendliness, and to better tailor it to your needs. WeTransfer also uses this information to verify that
users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests. These details can be provided to
third parties insofar as they cannot be traced back to you personally (i.e. it will not contain any Personal
Information).
As part of the Service, you may send a file to one or more recipients identified by a valid email address.
The message created by you will be sent from WeTransfer.com on your behalf to the email addresses you
have entered into the online form. These email addresses will be stored in the address book you have
created and will be used by WeTransfer.com only for the purpose of sending the email communication to
the addressee.
Use by third parties
Other than as described in the Privacy Policy, WeTransfer does not rent or share Personal Information
to or with third parties without your explicit consent. However, WeTransfer.com can provide your details
to third parties insofar as this is necessary for providing the Service to you, upon your request and/or
insofar as these details cannot be traced back to you personally. Finally, WeTransfer.com can provide
your details to third parties if they are obliged to do so pursuant to legal provisions, WeTransfer.com
is forced to do so as a result of a legal proceeding and/or in the event that WeTransfer.com regards it
necessary for the protection of its own rights.
5. In what manner does WeTransfer.com protect your personal Information?
WeTransfer takes safeguarding your Personal Information very seriously. WeTransfer employs generally-
accepted, industry-standard administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect the
Personal Information submitted to us from unauthorized access, both during transmission and once we
receive it. WeTransfer is using a high-tec datacenter.
However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic data storage is 100%
secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal
Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. WeTransfer is not responsible for any harm or
damage due to the security.

                                    PRIVACY POLICY                                                          p3
6. Is Personal Information transmitted outside the EU?
It may be required for technical and operational reasons that your Personal Information is transferred to
(servers of) companies affiliated to us in the United States or other countries outside Europe where the
regulations in the field of privacy protection might not provide the same protection as in the European
Union. By using the Service you are giving your consent to this.
7. Links to other sites
Our Site contains links to other web sites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner
ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third
party’s web site. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement
is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is
it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise
control over third party websites. These other web sites may place their own cookies or other files on
your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules
regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. WeTransfer.com does
not accept any responsibility or liability for (the operation and/or contents of) websites of third parties.
We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other web sites you visit.
8. Transfer of company
In the event of a further growth and development of WeTransfer.com it may be that one or more parts
of the assets of the company are transferred to a third party or that WeTransfer.com merges with a third
party. In that case your Personal Information will also be transferred.
9. Our policy towards minors
In principle everybody can use the Service. However, it is important that special legal rules apply to
persons who have not yet reached the age of sixteen (16). If you are not yet sixteen (16) you are required
to obtain the consent of your parents or legal guardian before you can use the Service. If you are below
the age of sixteen (16) and you don’t have this consent, you are not allowed to use the Service.
10. Contact and changes
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact WeTransfer at
info@wetransfer.com. If you want to know which Personal Information WeTransfer.com has recorded
about you, you can contact WeTransfer.com by means of the email address info@wetransfer.com. If you
have downloaded the Desktop Application and/or in the event you have an Account, you will be able to
access your Personal Information and change them if necessary.
